appletoolbox.com 2019-05-03

# Privacy - AppleToolBox

Updated: May 22nd, 2018

We value your trust, so we’ve strived to present this policy in clear, plain language:  We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which AppleToolbox collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://appletoolbox.com/ website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by AppleToolbox.

 **Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

We have updated the site with consent management for GDPR compliance as well. You can read about additional policy implementation by clicking [here.](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/appletoolbox.com)

Our user Forums require users to add name and email in order to continue. If you are not comfortable with sharing information, we recommend tha you use an annoymous name and an email. Information shared by you is not marketed or shared with any other third parties.

 **Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

 **Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

 **Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

 **Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

 **Links to Other Websites**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from the Service, including the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link or advertisement on our website, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies.

Social Media Widgets: Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. Social Media Features and Widgets are hosted by a third party. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

 **Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

 **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and [terms of service](https://appletoolbox.com/terms-of-use/ "Terms of Use"). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. By continuing to use our site, you accept our use of cookies, revised privacy policy and Terms of use.

 **Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
AppleToolbox  
https://appletoolbox.com/  
[[email protected]](https://appletoolbox.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Our mailing address

244 Lindero Ave, Long Beach, CA-90803 USA

This document was last updated on May 24, 2018
